{
    "subject": "resource/Berlin_Oranienburger_Stra\u00dfe_station",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe (in German Bahnhof Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe) is a railway station in the city of Berlin, Germany, located on Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe. It is served by the Berlin S-Bahn and local tram lines.",
    "human_readable": "Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe is a railway station in the city of Berlin, Germany, located on Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe. It is served by the Berlin S-Bahn and local tram lines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874973297119141,
            "question": "In which city is Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe railway station located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9785736203193665,
            "question": "What is the name of the street where Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe railway station is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9581940174102783,
            "question": "What type of transportation does Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9462683200836182,
            "question": "What are some of the services available at Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9293453097343445,
            "question": "Which transportation system connects to Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9242029786109924,
            "question": "Does Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station offer connections to other cities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8905068039894104,
            "question": "Is Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe a major transportation hub?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761011362075806,
            "question": "Besides trains, what other mode of transport connects to Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7656953930854797,
            "question": "Is Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe a bus stop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4722428321838379,
            "question": "What country is Berlin located in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe is a railway station in the city of Berlin, Germany, located on Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe. It is served by the Berlin S-Bahn and local tram lines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_849_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe a bus stop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_849_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides trains, what other mode of transport connects to Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_849_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe a major transportation hub?",
            "html": "dbpedia_849_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_849_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information that supports the statement \"Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe is a railway station in the city of Berlin, Germany, located on Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe. It is served by the Berlin S-Bahn and local tram lines.\" Therefore, the response is \"yes\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}